Huth, Geoffrey A.; Papers mss137
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1965-1966; 1969-2006; 12; 30.75 cubic ft.
  - Paper Publications, 1965-1966; 1969; 1972-2006; 12.1; 28.5 cubic ft.
    - Chace, Joel, Squares, with advertising flyer, 2004 (Box 3 (Bf-Ch) (12-Publications), Folder 113)
    - Chi Apa, #'s 24, 26, 29, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (Bf-Ch) (12-Publications), Folder 114)
    - Chimera, #20, 1987 (Box 3 (Bf-Ch) (12-Publications), Folder 115)
    - Chirodea, Doru, Aletheia Raped, 1989 (Box 3 (Bf-Ch) (12-Publications), Folder 116)
    - Chirodea, Doru, on metascrotum and infradeaths, 1990 (Box 3 (Bf-Ch) (12-Publications), Folder 117)
    - Chirodea, Doru, nonathambia, 1995 (Box 3 (Bf-Ch) (12-Publications), Folder 118)
    - Chirot, Dave, Anar Key Ology, 1999 (Box 3 (Bf-Ch) (12-Publications), Folder 119)
    - Chirot, Dave-Baptiste, Reverberations, 2005 (Box 3 (Bf-Ch) (12-Publications), Folder 120)
    - Chirot, Dave-Baptiste, Xerolage #32, Visual Poetry, copy art, collage, 2005 (Box 3 (Bf-Ch) (12-Publications), Folder 121)
    - Choplogic, #'s1-4, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (Bf-Ch) (12-Publications), Folder 122)
    - Chroronzon et Clarina, ca. 1988 (Box 3 (Bf-Ch) (12-Publications), Folder 123)
    - Ciccariello, Peter, Imaginal Landscapes, Xerolage 38, 2006 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Circulaire 132, #7, mention on page2, 2006 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Circular, #9, 11-12, 1987 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 3)
    - The Circus Bee, #54, 1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Cirque Divers, #125, 1990 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Claire, Eva, A Door in the Air, 1986 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 6)
    - The Clarke A. Sany Newsletter, Volume 4, #2, Volume 5, #3, 1990 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Cleaning Up the correlatives: 1CENT 3260, mention Geof Huth, 1990 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Clothing Optional, #0001, 1990 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Cloud, #'s 2-5, 7-10, 1987-1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Clown War, #10, 1975 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Cointet, Guy de [Qei no Mysxdod], Espahor ledet ko ulunerl, Undated (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Cointet, Guy de, TSNX C24VA7ME, A Play by Dr. Hun, 1974 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Collaborative Writing, 1990 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Cole, David, David Cole: Exhibition of Recent Works and an In-Gathering of Paint Stirrers, gift of Roy Arenella, 2000 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Coleman, Victor, Agua, 1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Coleman, Victor, Interruption #1, 2nd edition, 1994 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Coleman, Wanda, American Sonnets, 1994 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Co-Lingua: 15+ Years of NRG, Undated (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Collier, Paul G., Petril Wava, 1993 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Collier, Paul G., Petril Wava, 1993 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Collins, Sean, Instant Potatoes, 1993 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Colon, Carlos; and de Gruttola, Raffael, 2001 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Combien y a-t-il d'objets au monde, Tome 1 et 2, 1991 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Communication Irrationalism, mentions member Geof Huth, 1995 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Compost Modern Life, #'s1-4, 1989 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Computers: Keyboarding and Word Processing, 1986 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Cone, Jon, Poem for an Ex-Stripper Who..., 2001 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Connolly, Kevin, A Canadian in Paris, 1985 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Conti, Edmund, The Ed C. Scrolls, Undated (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Conti, Edmund, Eddies, 1994 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Conti, Edmund, Eddies, 1994 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 32)
    - Cory, Jean-Jacques, Lists, 1974 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 33)
    - The Coventry Reader, Volume II, #2, 1989 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Convulsions, Volume 1, #'s2 and 4, 1989 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Cook-Jolicour, Andrew; Leuck, Angela, General Motors Jazz Renga, 2005 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 36)
    - Cook's Night Out, Undated (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Corman, Cid, Auspices, Out of Series copy, 1979 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Corman, Cid, For Size, 1992 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Cory, Jean-Jacques, Lista, 1974 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 40)
    - Cosmic, Crowboy Comix, #1, 1982 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 41)
    - Couch, Clayton A., Artificial Lure, 2005 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 42)
    - Cramped and Wet, #'s4-5, 1989 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 43)
    - Cravan, Arthur, hereafter bp: an elegy that wouldn't continue, 1990 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 44)
    - Cravan, Arthur, the surf on q beach at night, 1983 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 45)
    - Creeping Bent, #'s 1, Undated (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 46)
    - Creeping Bent, #4-7, 1986-1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 47)
    - Critical Wave, #18, essay with name as Geof Huth, 1990 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 48)
    - Croton Bug, #3, 1994 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 49)
    - Crouse, John, cements, 2005 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 50)
    - Crouse, John and Reed Altemus, Macaroni, 2004 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 51)
    - Crouse, John and Andrew Topel, OH an Essay, 2005 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 52)
    - Crouse, John and Luc Fierens, Post flux post booklet #58, 2003 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 53)
    - Crouse, John and Andrew Topel, Yalp, 2003 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 54)
    - Crouse, John and Andrew Topel, Yalp/Poems, 2004 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 55)
    - Crozier, Robin and Jon M. Bennett, Overage, signed by authors, 1989 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 56)
    - Crozier, Robin and Jon M. Bennett, Seasoftfishook, 2001 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 57)
    - Crozier, Robin and Jon M. Bennett, Throne Fog, 1989 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 58)
    - Cult Comix, #'s 6-10, 1987-1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 59)
    - Cumberland Poetry Review, Volume III, #V, David Daniel Poem, 1983 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 60)
    - curry, jw, untitled, 1986 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 61)
    - curry, jw and Maurice Lucier, untitled color photocopy, 1991 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 62)
    - curry, jw, As Is or With, 1984 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 63)
    - curry, jw, The Basmajian Variations in A(minors), 1990 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 64)
    - curry, jw; Smith, Steven, Between: Sequence 1, 1989 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 65)
    - curry, jw and Steven Smith, Between: Sequence 1, 1989 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 66)
    - curry, jw, Boarding Zone, 2001 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 67)
    - curry, jw and Mark Laba, cream, Undated (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 68)
    - c[urry], jw, Dutton's Habit, 1989 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 69)
    - curry, jw and Peggy lefler, fiction Marks, signed by authors, 1982 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 70)
    - curry, jw, Guitar, 1991 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 71)
    - curry, jw and Mark Laba, Hardship, 1983 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 72)
    - curry, jw and Greg Evason, her ass falling off itself, 1987 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 73)
    - curry, jw, logical sequence #16, ca. 1984 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 74)
    - curry, jw, a mo(nu)ment for bpNichol, 1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 75)
    - curry, jw, night freight, 1990 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 76)
    - curry, jw, a node to d.a., 1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 77)
    - curry, jw, A Plea for Information of a Beepliographic Bent, Undated (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 78)
    - curry, jw, Please Help Johnny Coax the Cows Home, 1989 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 79)
    - curry, jw, Reflecting on the War, 2nd Edition, 1982 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 80)
    - curry, jw, a retrospective panhandle of jwcurry, ca. 1987 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 81)
    - curry, jw and Steven Venright, SHAKE a foot, 1984 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 82)
    - curry, jw and Mark Laba, Sinillogical Translations, Volume 5, 1985 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 83)
    - curry, jw, Qaani Lore, 1985 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 84)
    - curry, jw, RE:VIEWS:RE:SPONSES, 1991 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 85)
    - curry, jw, RE:VIEWS:RE:SPONSES, 1991 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 86)
    - curry, jw, Stucco Homes in Silk Wrappings, portrait 2, 1990 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 87)
    - curry, jw, Touch, 1984 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 88)
    - curry, jw, Trundling Into A Present, 2002 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 89)
    - curry, jw, twenty bottoms, Undated (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 90)
    - curry, jw, Video Hell, 1991 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 91)
    - curry, jw, Video Hell, 2nd edition, 1991 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 92)
    - Curvd H&z in Print, 1986 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 93)
    - Curvd H&z 426, 1997 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 94)
    - Czarnecki, Michael, Zoo Haiku, 2004 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 95)
    - D'Arpino, Tony, Tree, 1992 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 96)
    - dadata, Obsenic View, Undated (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 97)
    - Dalachinsky, Steve, Are We Not Men, 2005 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 98)
    - Dalachinsky, Steve and John M. Bennett, hands plus ditch Ferdinand, 2004 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 99)
    - Damon, Maria; and, mIEKAL, E.n.t.r.a.n.c.e.d., 2004 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 100)
    - Daniel, David, The Quick and the Dead, signed and inscribed, 1992 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 101)
    - DARE Newsletter, Dictionary of American Regional English, 2004 Fall; 2005 Winter (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 102)
    - DARE Newsletter, Dictionary of American Regional English, 2006 Winter (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 103)
    - dark water, Selected haiku by members of Haiku Deer Park, Toronto, Canada, 2005 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 104)
    - Darlington, Andrew, Almost Two Haiku, 1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 105)
    - Daurio, Don, The Electrician, 1991 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 106)
    - Davidson, Daniel, Weather, 1992 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 107)
    - David Thomas Roberts Broadside, #'s6-7, 1991 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 108)
    - Day, Linda, Maybe it's an old time already, 1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 109)
    - Deadhar, Angelee, drifting stars, 2004 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 110)
    - The Dead Rebel News, Volume 1, #1, 1991 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 111)
    - Dedora, B., Better Sentence Writing Made Easy, 1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 112)
    - Dedora, B., The Compact Edition of Huge, 1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 113)
    - Dedora, B., Hand Stamp, 1983 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 114)
    - delta: Revue internationale pour la poesie experimentale, #21, 2004 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 115)
    - DePaula, Alyssa, Talking to Tulips, design by Geof Huth, 2005 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 116)
    - Depew, Wally, Nine Essays on Concrete Poems, 1974 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 117)
    - de Sousa, elehna, Hawaii and back, 2005 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 118)
    - Diaz Rivera, Luis Roberto, Poesia, 1995 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 119)
    - deckle, pilliard, The Time Loop, Moebis Strip Comic Strip, 1982 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 120)
    - Dictionaire philosophique de poche, deuxieme edition, 1990 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 121)
    - DiMichele, Bill, 3 Spare Coats, 1985 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 122)
    - DiMichele, Bill, burnhole, Thanks for Printing a section, 1996 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 123)
    - DiMichele, Bill, capacity x, 1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 124)
    - DiMichele, Bill, fire engines, Arranged, 1987 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 125)
    - DiMichele, Bill, Heart on the Right, 1992 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 126)
    - DiMichele, Bill, Heart on the Right, 1992 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 127)
    - DiMichele, Bill and Crag Hill, Row War, 1986 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 128)
    - Dirt, #1-2, 2005 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 129)
    - Doctorovich, Fabio, Bribage Cartooniano, 1994 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 130)
    - Document-Page, #'s1-10, 1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 131)
    - Dolis, John, Bl( )nk Spaces, 1993 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 132)
    - dont talk, ca. 1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 133)
    - dop e, #'s5-6, ca. 1977 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 134)
    - Dorian, Colby, A PortHole 2 Hell..., 1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 135)
    - Dorian, Colby, Red Feathers, 1990 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 136)
    - Doug B, articulation Sought, 1991 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 137)
    - Dougherty, Jay, Coveringdeertrackswithwords, 1984 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 138)
    - Do Wnders Invention Manual, Volume 93, #1, 1988 (Box 4 (Ci-Do) (12-Publications), Folder 139)
    - Drafting #2, 2004 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Drake, Alan, Easter Island: The Ceremonial Center of Orongo, inscribed by author, thanks to Geof Huth page 100, 1992 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Drake, Alan, No Natural Vantage Point, mention dbqp, 1990 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Drake, Alan, Speedstorm to the Dreamvision, 1990 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Drake, Luigi-Bob, Male Art, 1989 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Drang Den, Volume 1, #'s 1-2, 4, 1989-1990 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Dreams and Nightmares, #'s 1-10, 14-15, 1986-1987 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Dreams and Nightmares, #'s 19/20-21, 23-40, 1987-1993 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Dreams and Nightmares, #'s 41-46, 50, 52, 55, 58, 61, 69, 1994-2004 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Dreams and Nightmares, flyer, 1989 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 10)
    - dreamtime talkingmail, #2, 1992 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 11)
    - dreamtime village, 1991 Summer (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 12)
    - dreamtime village, Undated (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Drop Forge #1-2, 4, 1995 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 14)
    - DSNA Newsletter, Volume 26, #1, 2002 Spring (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Dubrava, Patricia, Nothing to Show, 1985 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Dudley, Michael, a line, 2nd edition, 1983 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Dudley, Michael, uproar, 2004 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Duggan, MB, Work, 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Dunn, Lloyd, Aura, reprint of Tuyau #49, 1987 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Dunn, Lloyd, Inbetweening, 1989 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 21)
    - The Duplex Planet, #'s 15, 21-26, 28, 31, 33, 35-39, 41-42, 45-46, 105, 1980-1983; 1990 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Dutton, Paul, Faulty Basis, 1989 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Dutton, Paul, haiku, 1983 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Dutton, Paul, Phoenix, 1989 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Dweller, Cliff, This Candescent World, 1993 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Dweller, Cliff, This Candescent World, 1993 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Dweller, Cliff, The Persistence of Desire, 1991 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Eberly, John, At the still center, 1990 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Eberly, John, Automatics, 1986 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Eberly, John, The Basement, 1987 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Eberly, John, Bobo Yoyo Seeks the Truth!, 1985 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 32)
    - Eberly, John, The Book of Flies, thanks to Geof Huth, 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 33)
    - Eberly, John, Cartoon Brut, 1984 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Eberly, John, Poteau-Mitan, Jool, Circle of Poop, 1990 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Eberly, John, Cunt in my Face, 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 36)
    - Eberly, John, The Dialogues, 1990 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Eberly, John, Fluking, 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Eberly, John, The Garden, 1987 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Eberly, John, The Hieroglyphics Monad, ca. 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 40)
    - Eberly, John, The House, 1987 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 41)
    - Eberly, John, Jool Poteau-Mitan and Lampwild LaTour, The Juiciest Fruit, Undated (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 42)
    - Eberly, John, The Man Stories (6), ca. 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 43)
    - Eberly, John, PEEPHOLE/VOYAGER INOUT, 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 44)
    - Eberly, John, Quell, 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 45)
    - Eberly, John, Seasons Greetings from Mumbles, two colors, 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 46)
    - Eberly, John, Snake Paranoia in the Land of Oz, Undated (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 47)
    - Eberly, John, Ivan Hardone, psend., Spooie: A Novel, 1990 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 48)
    - Eberly, John, They Were in Love, 1986 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 49)
    - Eberly, John, Wear Your Lungs Like Heaven, 1990 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 50)
    - Eberly, John and Jake Berry, Gris Gris Malkuth, 1989 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 51)
    - effing magazine, #2-3, 2004-2005 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 52)
    - Eigner, Larry, A Count of Some Things, 1989? (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 53)
    - eleven, Winter 1984, Winter 1985, 1986, Spring 1987, Undated (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 54)
    - Elmslie, John, Dangerous Material, 1984 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 55)
    - Elsberg, John, Broken Poems for Evita, Undated (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 56)
    - Elsberg, John, Broken Poems for Evita, 1997 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 57)
    - Elton, Tom, Silent Companion, 2001 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 58)
    - Elvis' Ghost, 1989 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 59)
    - Embers, XVI:2, XVII:2, 1991; 1993 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 60)
    - Emo, 1984 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 61)
    - emPo Publications, catalog, 1989 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 62)
    - An Encyclopedia About Anyone, 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 63)
    - endwar, fall leaves, kite tail press #11, 2006 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 64)
    - endwar, fall leaves, kite tail press #14, 2006 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 65)
    - endwar, from i to iran, 1990 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 66)
    - endwar, from i to iran: further subverse wanderings of endwars, 1990 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 67)
    - endwar, i contact, Undated (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 68)
    - endwar, "An interior definition for Geof Huth", homage to Geof Huth, 2003 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 69)
    - endwar, Laughter, Symmetry, Discovery, Undated (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 70)
    - endwar, Out of WordS, 2003 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 71)
    - endwar, the pairwise interaction of nearest neighbors, 1990 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 72)
    - endwar, lmnts r, 1990 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 73)
    - endwar, rain, 1991 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 74)
    - endwar, the subverse wanders off the word, 1990 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 75)
    - endwar, this is about how you, 2005 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 76)
    - endwar, Unforgettable Fire, 1991 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 77)
    - endwar, With God, all things are possible, random access version, 1996 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 78)
    - Ensemble Vide, Dictionnaire Philosophique de poche, 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 79)
    - Ensemble Vide, Risquer sa vie n'est pas survivre, 1989 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 80)
    - Ensemble Vide, le terri, 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 81)
    - E.N.T.R.A.N.C.E.D., Maria Damon and Miekal and, agitate the linelength, Undated (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 82)
    - E.N.T.R.A.N.C.E.D., Without Knowing, 2004 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 83)
    - Entropic Broadside, #5, 1989 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 84)
    - The Environmental Forum, Volume V, #'s 1-3, 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 85)
    - Eotu, August Heat, Eotu 89, 1989 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 86)
    - Ernst, K.S., Sequencing, 1984 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 87)
    - Ernst, K.S., Sequencing, 1984 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 88)
    - Ernst, K.S., Visual Poetry Catalog, Three-Dimensional Pieces with Ceramic Letters, Undated (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 89)
    - Eshleman, Harry D., The Colors in the Sky, 1993 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 90)
    - Essary, Loris, grain, 1983 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 91)
    - E.S.T.U.D.I.O. #'s10, 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 92)
    - Estudio #11, 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 93)
    - E.S.T.U.D.I.O. #'s12-13, 1988 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 94)
    - E.S.T.U.D.I.O. #'s 14-15, 1989 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 95)
    - ESTUDIO #17-18, 1991 (Box 5 (Dr-Es) (12-Publications), Folder 96)
    - Eulipian, #1, 3-4, 1987-1989 (Box 6 (Eu-Fic) (12-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Evason, Greg, untitled, 1990 (Box 6 (Eu-Fic) (12-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Evason, Greg, 3 Windows, 1988 (Box 6 (Eu-Fic) (12-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Evason, Greg, 3 Windows, 1988 (Box 6 (Eu-Fic) (12-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Evason, Greg, Caves, 1985 (Box 6 (Eu-Fic) (12-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Evason, Greg, Codine, 1987 (Box 6 (Eu-Fic) (12-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Evason, G[reg], "Digging rain out of the", 1990 (Box 6 (Eu-Fic) (12-Publications), Folder 7)